<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Learn on AllThruSmartphone</title>
    <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/categories/learn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learn on AllThruSmartphone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:46:30 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/categories/learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is MMO?</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/what_is_mmo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:46:30 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/what_is_mmo/</guid>
      <description>Do you know why most people can&amp;rsquo;t make money online with affiliate marketing? Because they don&amp;rsquo;t know the NEW elaboration of MMO that I first introduced in this post. You can&amp;rsquo;t find it anywhere else&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is my smartphone-friendly side hustle?</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/smartphone_friendly_side_hustle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 02:13:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/smartphone_friendly_side_hustle/</guid>
      <description>I have mentioned 7 reasons why I think affilaite marketing is a smartphone-friendly side hustle and why I recommend it over other side hustles to begin with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The principles I follow</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/the_principles_i_follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:53:35 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/the_principles_i_follow/</guid>
      <description>If you ever tried make money online, you would know that how crazy the market is. Most vendors are launching shiny objects every now and then to attract new people, make more sale. Most newbies are trying to make sale and sale only. All of these will feel like an ecommerce site where people come to buy and vendors offers products. But this is not an ecommerce business. Make money online with affiliate marketing is based on transformation and long term strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to navigate this site</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/how_to_navigate_this_site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:14:30 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/how_to_navigate_this_site/</guid>
      <description>As I shared in the About page, I&amp;rsquo;m an open source enthusiast. I love those free and open source projects. But what it means for you? and why should you care?
It feels so amazing that those computer scientists working in open source projects are sharing their codes with the world. If you think deeply this is a contribution in a whole different level. As I am doing affiliate marketing for last 1+ year I realized that it is our natural tendency to protect our original contents from getting copied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My goal for this blog</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/my_goal_for_the_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:40:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/blog/learn/my_goal_for_the_blog/</guid>
      <description>I am imagining a future where smartphone will replace PCs in most tasks we do at present. I see the potential of smartphone &amp;ndash; it can be deployed everywhere, even in remote location&amp;hellip; I have seen many places in my country where there are people using smartphones to stay connected but we can&amp;rsquo;t give a PC to those areas.
Smartphone has got some cool advantages over PCs, for example, A PC requires a setup but a smartphone requires no setup.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
