<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>about on AllThruSmartphone</title>
    <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/tags/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in about on AllThruSmartphone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 22:05:14 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the author</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/about/about-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 22:05:14 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/about/about-author/</guid>
      <description>Shafat M. I am the author of this blog from Bangladesh&amp;hellip;here are some facts about me:
I am a millennial, born in 1990&amp;hellip; I am a smartphone, tech, open source, management, productivity and currently online marketing enthusiast&amp;hellip; I completed BBA and MBA in Human Resources Management&amp;hellip; I contributed to a top management forum for 3 years with my contents on HRM and Productivity&amp;hellip; I have grown up with computer since 2000 and with smartphone since 2016&amp;hellip; I am using solely Linux OS (KDE Neon) in my home PC for 3+ years now&amp;hellip; I work at a religious org not for making money but for serving entirely&amp;hellip; I started learning and doing a side hustle in May 2022 to make some money at my leisure and do some charity&amp;hellip; I have helped hundreds of newbies to learn affiliate marketing from my free resources and guidance since then&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About the blog</title>
      <link>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/about/about-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 22:05:14 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://allthrusmartphone.xyz/about/about-site/</guid>
      <description>allthrusmartphone.xyz A smartphone lifestyle focused blog authored by Shafat M.
Slowly and steadily we are moving towards a world where our smartphones will dominate everything &amp;ndash; from our life to our education to our business. Through this blog, the author is going to educate and inspire Gen X, Y and Z on how to use this little workhorse for learning, earning, and productivity so that they can better prepare themselves for the future.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
